dealcomet.com 2010-12-08

# Privacy Policy - Deal Scorer

##  What Personal Information About Me Does Deal Scorer Gather?

####  Information You Give Us:

We collect and store any information you enter on our website or give us in any other way. We use this information to provide you service and to communciate with you. 

####  Automatic Information:

Like many web sites on the internet, Deal Scorer uses cookies to collect information on you. We also recieve information from your browser. 

##  Does Deal Scorer Share the Information It Receives?

Yes, we do share information as described below. 

  1. **Advertisers:** We share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisiers. This information is not linked to personal information that can identify the individual from where the data was collected. 
  2. **Service Providers:** We use other companies and individuals for services on our behalf. These parties may aggregate and use information collected from our website. For example, we may use Google Analytics to collect and aggregate information about our visitors.
  3. **Business Transfer:** In the course of our business, we might be acquired by another company or entitiy. In such a transaction, cutomer information is generally transferred as one of the acquired business assets. 
  4. **Compliance:** We may release information when we believe it is appropriate in order to comply with law, to enforce or apply any agreements, or to protect the rights and safety of our company and users. This may include providing information to companies or organizations for fraud detection / prevention.

##  Outbound Links

Deal Scorer may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the Privacy Policies or Terms of Use of other sites. We encourage you to review the Privacy Policy and Terms of Use of such other sites. This Privacy Policy only applies to this Website. 

##  Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions 

If you choose to visit Deal Scorer, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Washington. If you have any concern about privacy at Deal Scorer, please send us a thorough description using our contact form located here, and we will try to resolve it. This Notice and the Terms of Use is subject to change , and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Notice in effect at the time of use. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions (but we are under no obligation to). You should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes.
